Sub by: ConcacSUB
Rate me on Opensubtitle
hi my name is Peter Parker
you don't remember me
but I have something to tell you that's gonna sound crazy
but it's the truth
and I know you're gonna believe me
because you're very good at telling when I'm lying
Evie can you check the calibration of my targeting matrix
that doesn't feel zeroed in to me
checking target calibration
hey Evie
take 5 standing by
we used to know each other
we were together
but something bad was gonna happen
and the only way to stop it was to make everyone forget me
first day at MIT let's go
oh my gosh we're here
we made it oh MJ
come on including you
pretend like you're not the happiest you've ever been
in your entire life right now
I can't
because I'm not just Peter Parker
I'm Spider Man I'm really
really understanding the culture out here in Boston
it's just so different
and sometimes Spider Man has to do the hard thing
even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart
but everyone here is like park the car by the Haba
and maybe that's my responsibility
I don't know how to talk to live alone with the truth
but the truth is MJ that I love you
and I hope that deep down
something inside of you remembers that you love me too
suspect is 5 8 to 5 10 medium build
but until then I'm just gonna be Spider Man
incoming
members of the Manfredi crime syndicate
were apprehended by Spider Man yesterday
hey we live on the same floor
oh
cool
does anybody ever come up here
not unless they like us best us
we've just been using it for storage
that's perfect
hey everyone sophomore year and that is back older
wiser flyer haha
let's go whoa
what is on your face how do you feel about it
I mean you look like an assistant coach
you sure you wanna do this scorpion
did you miss me Spidey
if I drop you from here
how long do you think it would take you to hit the ground
well I don't know
you tell me
let's end this on a high note huh
Yo Lonnie
what happened the wolf
all the evidence you're gonna need is in the trunk of his car
you trying to take my job
Spider Man hey
you guys are the professionals I'm just a volunteer
it's a new New York thanks to Spider Man
crime rates have dropped to a record low
police and damage control give much of the credit to the masked hero
initiate hug test armed robbery at Civic Union Bank
in the past six months
he has taken down every major crime lord across the five boroughs
including the superpowered ninja group the hand
he is the pride of New York City
the hero every grown up relies on and every kid wants to be
final semester MIT oh my gosh
we're graduating in a month
we've made so many memories
where do I begin
night swimming in the Charles River with Jim and Wiley
the infamous food fight at the Banana Lounge
pulling all nighters in stud 5 with MJ and Nate dog
it feels like yesterday I was sitting on a roof with MJ
dreaming about coming here together
and I still can't believe we did it
I'm so grateful for all the friends that I've made
I couldn't imagine going through this with anyone else
dad who do you think is actually watching these
uh I
I don't know but maybe someone
OK well
bye someone what
bye we're done no
I mean we're talking about Downtown Brooklyn in broad daylight
high profile job like that
you know that Fazel was involved
yeah I hear you
but can you prove it yeah
I'm going through his financial records
and I'm following his crew every night
do you do anything besides work
you know the saying you do something you love
you don't work a day in your life
came here to that mom
where's my calculator I don't know
trust me alright
being married to the job never ends well
don't worry about it I'll be okay
oh yeah
you still getting them headaches though
uh yeah
but um
but I'll be fine I don't know man
I think your body's trying to tell you something
like you need to get out of that suit every once in a while mom
do you know where my calculator is I don't know puppy
what you need is some real human connection
oh what
and we're not connecting nah dude
I don't know your name your face or nothing about you
I don't think you've ever asked me a question about my life
sure I have yeah
what are my kids names uh
well for starters
your son's name is Poppy hahaha
is it Spider Man I can't tell you that sweetheart
that means it's Spider Man oh gosh
a hijack tank is heading southbound past 34th Street
all available units respond
hey you getting this more work
lucky you okay
I'll see you out there I'm so sorry I gotta go
wow wow
I got you Spidey no
no I don't need you
hey that's enough
you okay kid yeah
you're okay see you later
you wouldn't know it just by looking at it
but this very street was completely destroyed
in the battle of New York
come on come on
ah ah ah
come on
hey
what the hell Frank you just hit me with a van
quit your whimpering we're not doing that again Frank
you goddamn right we're not
this time you're gonna get the hell out of my way well
you mean instead of saving your life
I gotta talk about that Staten Island bullshit again
no well
you said it not me
look man you can't just shoot yourself out of every situation
innocent people get hurt what do you think's the range of that tank
dumb dumb
hahaha
shoot yourself
jackass
this freaking guy
mother
go home Frank
i'mma kill this kid
the wolf you gonna stop that thing or what
it's heading straight for the damage control detention center
I'm trying try harder
there's a lot of scary dudes locked up in there
well who do you think put them in there
let's go scorpion
moving day
all right everybody clear out
this guy is armed and dangerous
uh
get out of the vehicle ma'am
I was thinking the same thing
Spider Man
where am I
what the
keep her for questioning clear the building
enjoy the ride scorpion
you won't be seeing much daylight in supermax
scorpions are nocturnal buddy
the building is under attack
get the prisoner out of here now
you gotta take off now the building is in breach go
go
fire it up go go
change of plans
take him to the helicopter at Bellevue
what that's an order from Director Mexico
go now copy that
hey what
how did I get up here uh
Spiderman
save me would you
who are you
you can see me tell me who you are
you first
hey
you pushed me out
interesting what the hell was that
did you just try to jump into my mind
you know the whole time you've been chasing me
you forgot to ask yourself a very important question
what's in the tank
Spiderman
what just happened
I don't know
hey good job you guys okay
you good I swear all the things they said I did
I don't remember doing any of them
it's okay it's okay look
let these people take good care of you
I would never hurt you okay
I love you Spider Man yeah
alright buddy
alright hey
what you got here get this chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue
10 minutes later a guard walked him right out the door what
uh huh what about the tank
stolen from the damage control warehouse in Brooklyn
driver was a janitor who worked there
you got a motive Nada and no criminal record
scorpion must have gotten to her somehow
yeah maybe
what do you mean maybe I mean I
I don't know but I know someone that might
where you going you keep following the leads on Scorpion
I'm gonna go talk to someone
я
считаю надрать и хорошо и
редко почти как на эльдорадо как на моём авто
hi uh is this 32 50 Brighton beach Farah Yasser Srova
okay I think I know what that means
take off your clothes
uh what you don't wear clothes in the banya
ditch the leotard
this is not a leotard your text said that this was your office
this is my office
get in
haha uh I'm fine thanks I'll just what what haha my office my rules
this way you get to enjoy a nice relaxing soak
and I get to see that you don't have any weapons and we both win
okay
haha
really but you never take that off
no I
you know it defeats the whole anonymous thing
even for your girlfriend or boyfriend or whatever
there's a lot of conjecture online and super graphic artwork
have you seen the one with you and the 10 mysterious wait yeah
yeah I
I've I've
I've seen it I
I it's hard to unsee
to be honest but look
I don't have anyone I just kind of keep to myself
all by yourself all the time
no wonder you're so sad I'm not so sad
a little bit
could we just talk about what I came here to talk to you about
the attack on damage control yes
so that is more your area
like small potato stuff
whereas the new Avengers are focusing on big potato stuff
right okay
well there's more to it than that
you know the um
the driver and the others who were helping
it was like someone was talking to me through them
like someone was looking at me through their eyes
and you're wondering if it's mind control
exactly like how they used on me in the Red Room
exactly and the other weirdos right right
no I don't think so
I actually think it's probably more like possession possession
hmm hmm
like a ghost or a demon or in Russia
we have Leshi Leshi rules the forest and can possess
sorry whatever it is
they're looking for something
this is the fourth attack on the damage control facility this month
and what do you think they're looking for
I don't know but you know what
after the attack today
there was a cross agency cyber security alert that got triggered
someone accessed a damage control restricted servers
using credentials from 30 employees from the waste station
they all searched for the same thing
VMAX
what does that mean I mean
it could be alien tech or secretive weapon programs or launch codes or
I don't know this is for you to figure out
this is small baby potato stuff
not OK big potato brain stuff
Jeez maybe I'll just go ask damage control myself
you know you're not completely anonymous anymore
I've seen your belly button
okay bye
please repeat the sentence strictly in lower case
without punctuation and text formatting
oh god
hi I got an appointment with uh
Director Metzger yes
please step through the scanner
enhanced human detected
superior strength
superior agility
heightened senses
exogenist DNA arachnid
please remove your face covering for identity scan
oh no I can't do that
that's not a failure
to remove your face covering will result in defensive measures
defensive measures what are you talking about
whoa whoa
whoa guys
guys guys
I can't take my mask off I'm Spider Man
he's alright at ease
my apologies
we are so glad you're here
Bill Metzger director of Damage Control
how are you I'm good
thank you we had to beef up security around here
but I hope we didn't give you a fright
no not at all
alright come on this way
this floor is mostly research and administrative
downstairs we have incident clean up laboratories
agent training oh hey
what are they doing here it's okay
the hand works for us now
after you brought them in
I realized that fundamentally they're a group of kids without a leader
all they needed was a little direction
and suddenly all the things that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable part of our security team
you can look at the many threats that face us and see only danger
or you can see opportunity
uh okay
wow look at that
in the hands of shocker these are a nuisance
but it doesn't mean we can't learn from the technology
or respect the innovation
our mission is to redirect destructive energy into something useful
that's the true meaning of damage control
be careful with that
right this way
I uh
I wanted to talk to you about the recent attacks on the agency
there's been four right
please have a seat
you are right it appears we're faced with a threat we can't control
one we can't even see
but you can
I saw the security footage
I also read detective de Wolf's report
I believe you understand exactly what we're up against
someone or something that can hop into people's minds
but not yours no
I mean it tried but it couldn't
I'm gonna be honest with you
we're on our heels right now
God forbid
if we were to get in here and find whatever it is it's looking for
the consequences could be unimaginable
well let me guess is whatever it's looking for in that giant vault
there are some things because of the nature of my job
I cannot tell you but I believe you are our best defense against this
you're the only one who can sense it
you're the only one who's immune to it
I'm counting on you to defeat it
that's pretty good speech director
I'll do everything that I can I promise
well then consider yourself a friend of damage control
thank you
I'll be in touch
oh uh
I wanted to ask um
the phrase VMAX doesn't mean anything to you does it
no
where'd you hear that oh
it's just you know
nature of being a superhero
there are some things I just can't tell you
anyway I'll see you later
you guys are doing great keep it up
I don't think Metzger knows any more than we do
but I told him I'd do whatever I can to help
you wanna help the best thing you could do is find Scorpion
he's our only lead yeah
I know I have every camera in the city
running a facial recognition scan for him
that sounds super illegal
Spider Man i'mma pretend
I didn't hear that yeah
probably for the best but look
if he shows his face we'll know
do you have any mini cakes
none of yet thanks
I'll call you back
uh huh
easy
hey uh
also you got any sharp fire energy yeah
oh no
no no
I I
I don't want any that that stuff will kill you
you know all my friends were drinking them during the finals
and now they're addicted so I'm gonna need you to not sell me any
memorize my face
please do not sell this guy any shark fire
sure whatever
actually I'll take one last one
maybe two and then never sell me any
damn it
I had to tell you
oh man
oh yes
oh my God appreciate you
let's go
let's go what time do you guys get here
I think I like it I think I like it
that's how my life is I couldn't find this
you need a drink take this
take this come on
I'm not a savior I wish to save you
lesson I Learned my lesson
oh
oh um
Steve stumbled across my board
I'm not one of those weirdos
I swear
he actually saved me and my friend's lives a few times in high school
oh cool
yeah yeah
and ever since I've just been trying to figure out who he is
not not to unmask him to the world or anything
just to know you know
and to hopefully thank him face to face
I actually created this app that monitors his sightings
well you created Spidey Tracker
you heard of it nice
where is Spider Man chat room
right there
now we know he's definitely from Queens
not the biggest revelation
but I have been able to narrow it down to two prime suspects
yeah if you knew who they were
it would really blow your mind
I'm sure
Ned by the way
oh I'm um
god there's like 50 people in our apartment
statistically speaking that means at least two of them are sociopaths
which is kind of cool
nice flowers
oh they're a uh
a housewarming gift really
yeah oh OK
haha most people just brought beer and chips
it's very nice uh
I'm MJ
I'm a I'm a Maine
I'm Maynard
oh you two don't know each other
no I'm a neighbor friendly neighbor
sorry so how was the interview
I'm gonna go put these in water
it was nice to meet you Maynard nerd Maynard yeah
did you go please tell me that you went yeah
no I went and
and I got the job oh my God MJ
that's amazing I turned it down
what yeah
I don't wanna work for some soulless corporation
they're not all soulless
okay they're all mostly soulless
but don't you want like health insurance
yeah of course I do
but what cost depends on your deductible
oh you mean like your principles
yes sorry
I don't know I know it sounds cheesy
but
something is just telling me that
I'm supposed to be waiting for something great
you know
okay um
to uh
waiting for something great waiting for something great well
the wait is over oh hahaha
your new home dude this is top shelf just like you oh
I wanna hide this
I lifted this off of him again
but what if Ned needs the fire of 1.000 sharks
you mean heart palpitations
you can't save everyone I can try
that's my girl
I'm sorry I gotta
when we get into MIT we should live together yeah
for sure yeah
I'd love that be a fresh start and we'll all be together
yeah no
you're right yeah fresh start
you're gonna forget who I am forget who you are
what are you talking about
it's okay
I'm gonna come and find you and I'll explain everything I love sweet
wait and tell me when you see me again
my name is Peter Parker and I like a coffee
is there anything else
no
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
hey
you think you don't have to listen to me now I've got powers hahaha
you know
this this whole thing can get really scary you know that
well yeah
it's already pretty scary
yeah
and things can change very quickly
in ways that we can't even imagine right now
believe me I know
I don't think you do know
what you mean
oh God
please repeat the sentence
strictly lower case without punctuation and text formatting
I uh
I live here I just um
I'm gonna grab my stuff
is that my shirt
no
oh cute dog oh shit
hi Peter
you have 107 new alerts please check backlog
what is happening
the results of your body scan
show a surge in the hormones associated with your arachnid DNA
resulting in the formation of organic web spinnerets
and dangerously heightened sensory receptors okay
but I I
I feel fine prolonged isolation
or emotional trauma could be contributing to this sudden change
have you experienced any recent traumatic events
Peter
I'm fine Evie
you don't seem fine I recommend you take some time to rebalance
well that's not really an option is it
mechanical web shooters and organic webs cannot be used simultaneously
come on Peter
alert senses are overloaded
alert senses are overloaded senses are alert
what the hell was that
your heightened senses are taking in too much information at once
okay it's okay
it's okay alright
organic webs Peter too had him
he was cool you're cool
oh oh my God
that's hideous oh okay here we go
OK that didn't work
organic webs come on man webs
stop
what's going on Evie
shots fired at the damage control data center in Manhattan
suspect facial match with Scorpion okay
I'm on my way come on 3
2 1 go
web stop
web stop web stop
I'm sorry I'm sorry
web stop oh God
oh crap
stop stop stop
I don't know what you're looking for I'm looking for VMAX
I don't know anything I'll see for myself
oh God
I'm sorry I'm late
I've had a really crazy day
scorpion do we really gotta keep doing this
my head is killing me
you think I'm scorpion
what's happening to you
you can't sense me anymore
you what's going on with you Spider Man
warning arachnid hormones increasing
who are you do you know who you are
we need some help over here
Spider Man
what the hell somebody get a medic
the wolf is she hurt
is she okay is she okay
no just let me go
don't what is going on with you
that wasn't Scorpion okay
I mean it it was but
but he was possessed by whatever hijack Titanic okay
look please can I just slow down
listen I don't know what this is
but I need you to pull it together you almost killed a cop
this isn't you I know
I'm sorry if you act like this again
I cannot protect you whatever this is you need to fix it
through lettuce chromodynamics
we can arrange time and space in a grid
which allows us to simulate the quarks binding into the protons
Cindy is this a question about protons or more stuff about Avengers
okay guys I love to tell stories but you know I
I gotta teach you some physics at some point here
alright let it rip Cindy
if Thanos was so worried about overpopulation
why didn't he just use the magic glove to make more food
Arthur you wanna answer that question
Hulk
no
uh excuse me Doctor Banner
I am uh
you okay yeah
sorry it's just a headache um
have you got a minute I wanted to talk to you about your inhibitor
oh sure
don't worry it's got fail safes
I'm not gonna turn into the big green
raging monster machine in the cafeteria
but if you do see me with this thing off run
no
haha
no but you're using target specific short interfering RNA right
it's like gene silencing you're just incorporating the gamma radiation
what did you say your name was
uh Ned please
so you found a way to suppress the expression of DNA
even as it's undergoing the mutation due to gamma radiation right
yes okay
so my question is
would that same thing be possible with DNA that's mutating
for another reason
what's the reason
I don't know uh
let's say that the
the host genome is mixed with some kind of foreign DNA theoretically
theoretically yes
that's possible yes
so could you suppress only some parts of that DNA expression
like the bad aspects but just keep all of the good stuff
you mean like if I wanted to keep some parts of Hulk but not others
right it would be enormously dangerous and complex
but if you were able to target the correct mrna strand
possibly wait so you could just turn the mutating gene on and off
as long as you do it before the mrna transcription maybe
I mean if you apply the same thinking
you could even develop some kind of automatic inhibitor
that would just adjust to any type of mutation
well now
you're talking about a universal inhibitor
that would control anyone who has any powers
it's a dangerous idea
yeah but it's theoretical right
you're not one of my students are you
no I'm a grad student
I've uh
I've taken enough of your time
I gotta get some books back to the library the library is that way
right right
how would you decide
what's that
well what parts of nature are good or bad
what if you're trying to
control the expression of something that needs to be expressed
good luck with your studies Ned
thank you professor
like reptiles amphibians and anthropods
spiders shed skin at key points in their life cycle
the process is known as molting
4th inhibitor prototype complete
while molting is a natural part of a spider's life cycle
it can leave the spider vulnerable
upload inhibitor beta build 7 uploaded
would you like to run a test
yeah run it
spiders have three stages in their life cycle
each stage is characterized by physical
changes
with the largest changes occurring during the beautiful transition
to adulthood
for those who make it through
molting amounts to a kind of rebirth
can you turn that spider stuff off
turning off video inhibitor active
here we go come on come on
keep an eye on my vitals
inhibitor engaged
suppressing arachnid hormones to your baseline levels
okay
all right Evie
let's do this initiating field Test one
that's working Alert
inhibitor is overheating functionality reducing
yeah I'm sensing that alert senses are overloaded alert alert
alert alert
web grenades activated
oh shit
inhibitor field test 1 failure
Yo Spider Man
you okay yeah
I'm just trying out some new tech
oh yeah
to get rid of that monster inside you
still can't sense me huh
guess your technology isn't working
you know you're the only person I met that I can't hop into
I'm sure that's really frustrating for you
I'll get in there one day what do you want
I wanna know why a half human
half spider would decide to work for an organization
whose sworn mission is to hunt down anybody who's different
damage control isn't after you because you're different
they're hunting you down because you're dangerous
now what do you want
since you're a very simple spider
let me spell it out for you
damage control has something that I need
oh you mean VMAX
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it
but you keep getting in my way
I will always be in your way
are you sure about that Peter Parker
you know your apartment is kind of like a parody where you think a sad
single guy in his 20s might live
take out containers free weights
protein powder
hahaha
you're bluffing you know
you're not hard to track down Pete
well at least not for someone like me
I did find one interesting thing though
and of all places
coffee cup
EV display homework station
you spent four years erasing Peter Parker from existence
no wonder this Spider's trying to swallow up the man
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you
I think I might go see how she's doing
I'm not gonna let that happen
no her roommate was nice enough to post a new address online
how about this I'll race you there
if you touch her better start swinging I'm fast
hey it's a long way to MJ's
you better pick up the pace
Evie track physical anomalies
searching for physical anomalies between subjects please stand by
thank you all so much for coming today
oh
I'm sorry about that
give it up for Spider Man in a race for the love of his life
and it's not looking good
come on Spidey
keep up
excuse me sorry
EV run these numbers with the others
analyzing jump distances for patterns
give me that jump data calculating
come on I need an answer
calculations complete
you have a limit to your jump
radius don't you 33 feet
I don't see anybody up here for you to hop into very clever
like I said you're not getting near her
oh
hey hey hey
I'm sorry but you're in danger
where's your roommate what
where is Ned uh
in Boston with friends why
OK good
you gotta come with me what
I don't know if you're the real Spider Man
I'm not coming with you we don't have time for this
please come on you need to get out of my apartment look
this is gonna sound insane
but there is someone who is after you who is really dangerous okay
and I promised you that I would keep you safe
please you just have to trust me come on
fine
when will you stop
when we stop
are you okay yeah
yeah I'm fine okay
we should be safe up here okay
well safe from what
uh
I'm not entirely sure okay
well what do they want with me
I don't know you don't know it
it doesn't make any sense
why would they choose me um
I wish I could tell you I just uh
we knew each other didn't we
what
it's the only explanation
it's been driving me crazy for years
all the times that Spider Man saved either me or Ned
it was the Washington Monument
and then it was London and Prague and the Night Monkey
I mean twice as a coincidence but over and over again
we knew each other tell me I'm wrong
wait you're wrong
what were we were we classmates or our friends or something
like I I don't know what you're talking about were we something more
I just I can't
I can't remember and I feel like someone scrambled my brain
and you're the only one who would know why
this is crazy I
I know that you can't tell me the truth
but I need to know
maybe there's a part of me that still remembers
Peter
I miss you so much
I can't believe you figured it out I did
go ahead Peter
touch her
hold her
you've been wanting to for so long
true love's kiss breaks the spell and reunites the star crossed lovers
MJ would vomit
you really are a simple spider aren't you
I see why you like her
she's uh
she's smart
funny and a little dark and twisted
I mean it is sad
there is like no thoughts of you in here whatsoever
but you knew that didn't you
you're a monster
if you loved someone the way that I love her
then you'd know that what you're doing right now is unforgivable
oh is that so
you know
some people would kill to hold the person they love one last time
stop it now
you're running out of time Peter
soon enough
it won't just be your friends who don't remember Peter Parker
maybe you should write a letter to yourself
get out of her
who's the monster now Peter
no no no
oh God oh God please no
come on come on
oh thank God
oh thank God oh
you're okay oh
you're okay I'm so sorry
stop wait
wait stop
stop please
I'll quit you you win
you win you win just don't hurt her
you're a mess Spider Man
anytime I want I can be anyone I want
so you can't protect MJ even from herself
it really is a nice letter
little heavy handed not bad
you're okay I'm gonna take you someplace safe what
take me to 3 1
6 5 Lafayette Street
navigating to Empire State University
I got you I got you
are you sure yep
OK cause I feel like I'm slipping a little bit
you're not slipping OK
you're OK you're OK
you're OK yeah
yeah I'm fine I'm fine
OK can we just slow down for like two seconds
we're almost there yeah
yeah but you just told me I was mind controlled
well not technically
and you're lucky I believe in that stuff OK
because governments have been doing it for years
especially the French are you OK
yeah look sorry
I'm just trying to take you someplace safe OK
I don't feel safe
you losing it kid
thought you'd be able to see that coming a mile away
what is wrong with you you could have killed us
excuse me you show
up to my house unannounced
what do you think is gonna happen
wait this is your house
no don't don't
who the hell is that who the hell are you
well I
I she's um uh
you know no
I don't know that's why I just asked you
she's in danger Frank
look I need your help okay
yeah looks like it
well come on
you owe me ah fuck
aren't you sick of this story
Staten Island no Staten Island
what more do you want me to do
I literally saved your life
you're out of your mind kid
but I gotta save it twice to get a favor
that guy couldn't hit me with a handful of rice
what does that sound like to you
I have a drug dealer that's gonna shoot a guy
and I sent the gun right there out of the drug dealer's back
and I know exactly what I'm doing
kick that drug dealer back into the water
OK fine
go ahead what does that sound like to you
I don't care I just wanna go home
that's an excellent idea kick rocks
go home no
no wait
wait wait Frank
Frank Frank
Frank wait please
I have got to keep her safe
OK and I don't have anywhere else to go
you like chili
I made chili
alright just watch out for the claymores
I'm gonna pick up pieces of you for the next two weeks
hey I definitely would not eat that chili
so you're telling me
that maniac behind all that tank nonsense
is nothing but a goddamn teenager
and it's not just the tank
it's every attack on damage control this past month
how does a kid learn how to drive a tank
I don't know Frank
beat your ass all over the street like that
she did not beat my ass
this your family
you get the hell away from that
look I got one rule in this house
you don't touch anything you don't move anything
you sure as shit don't ask me any goddamn questions about anything
so 3 rules
ask you why you like her
go put some pants on
don't touch the chili
I like him
of course you do
so I managed to pull this image from my hood
and run it through the system
who is she until a couple months ago nobody
she was in and out of foster care
psych hospitals
and then eventually she ran away and dropped off the grid
there's hardly any information about her that hasn't been scrubbed
but she's classified as a telepath and now we have a name
Jean Grey
yeah these are the damage control sites that she hasn't hit yet
so if she surfaces then my facial tracking program will pick her up
right oh yeah what then
well don't worry about what then
just look after her don't worry about it huh
I'm just supposed to sit here
babysit your girlfriend I don't
know well she's not my girlfriend
so alright look
what's the plan huh
just gonna hope that your facial tracking program works
and you get yourself killed
I gotta watch her the rest of my life I'm not gonna get killed Frank
I can catch her okay
I just I just have to fix my inhibitor and then I'll be good to go
what do you need to do that
haha Frank
you do not have what I need to do that okay
hey you got some mouth on you
what do you think you have
an anti static mat a tonal probe and micro tools
I got all that shit what for bombs bingo
unbelievable
hey do you think it's safe to maybe call someone and let them know
I'm okay
uh
like your boyfriend
no like my roommate
oh um
I don't think that's such a good idea
you know because she already knows who he is
and she can inhabit anyone she wants right
yeah yeah yeah
you're right sorry
no it's fine
I I totally get it
if I called my boyfriend
he just asked me a bunch of questions that I couldn't answer
and then he'd tell me I was being withholding again withholding yep
sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a jerk
why do you think you're withholding
I don't know you tell me mass vigilante behind the curtain
um haha okay I see your point
so what about you what about me
well do you have a Mrs Spider Man
do I have a Mrs Spider Man um
no no
why not why not because I'm
I'm too withholding obviously
welcome to the club ha ha
there was someone really yeah
yeah yeah
what happened
I uh
I had to let her go to keep her safe
I'm sorry that must have been really hard for you
yeah it was yeah it is it is really hard
oh
are you okay yeah
yeah yeah
I'm okay I
you know what it's gonna come over
hold on hold on
what's going on um
it just keeps overheating on me
it's been stumping me for days
before I switched to aerospace
I was gonna major in biochemical engineering
so do you mind if I oh yeah
for sure here there you go
wow
so does the device itself
I mean does it generate any kind of radiation or a magnetic field
cause that would definitely interfere
oh yeah it has a micro magnetic field
but I accounted for that in the design okay
well what about your suit
oh it actually dissipates into the fabric
which is pretty cool
okay
what about those
what about what
your goggles or whatever you call them
uh they would create a field
it would be tiny but
but it's on your head which is very close to the inhibitor
which is probably why it's overheating Omg that is genius
okay this has to work
inhibitor engaged
suppressing selected arachnid hormones
okay that feels better
that feels totally better
oh my head feels so clear oh
and I'm not shooting organic webs
oh my God MJ
that like totally worked
you know this is some really intense stuff you're working on here
well yeah it's really important
yeah but this is like
I mean this is like altering your DNA
I mean this is the kind of stuff you put on like
I don't know like a monster
well if you seen what's been happening to me over the last couple days
and then you might understand yeah
well I've been with you for the last few hours
and that's not what I've seen and what have you seen
from my side of the curtain
a really good guy who might just be changing
I don't mean to overstep I'll uh
let you get back to it
can't sleep either huh
you want coffee
sure
you get your shit fixed
yeah I've been wearing it all night
so far so good
I made this other one universal
so if I could get it on Jean
it should completely shut down her powers
you know what else will work
you just shoot her nice
Jesus Christ
that's gotta be the goofiest shit I ever seen in my life
well you can't even take the mask off
drink a cup of coffee
don't take it personally Frank it
stays on for everybody
even her
who is she kid I don't know
that's horseshit who is she
I'm telling you I don't know who she is doing you care about her
you pretend you don't care about her look
I don't know who she is Frank okay
I don't have anybody I'm like you
I just keep to myself you like me
what do you know about me kid
you think this is a choice
living like this is a lifestyle
is that what you think kid this is a sentence
if I had one second
people I love are still breathing
you think I'd be hiding behind a mask
you think I pretend to be something that I'm not
acting like a goddamn coward
I got a facial match
she's at the damage control HQ in Manhattan
I gotta go okay
she's gonna be okay I'll see to it
thanks Frank
hey
just gonna let him go by himself
you know I think he might need you
hey
kinda like you needed him on Staten Island
you can't hide from me forever Bill
you've got a strong door but it's the wall you have to worry about
who are you and what do you want
I'm Jean Grey and you know what I want
あるてこっちだあの化け物が来る前に逃げるんだ
Jean you looked me up I'm blushing
I told you what would happen to your girl if you got in my way
you're not getting near her again
and you're definitely not getting inside that vault
maybe not
but this guy might
Jean you don't know what you're dealing with
you know you and banner have a lot in common
both fighting a losing battle against the monster that lives inside
you Jean
this is the Hulk you can't defeat
what the hell
oh I see
trying to muzzle me like you muzzle yourself
I can't let you in there whatever VMAX is
you're not getting it like hell I'm not
don't do this save your breath
Frank what are you doing here
what you think I'm doing I'm saving your ass
this is way above your pay grade we're fighting the Hulk
really
get out
stop shooting him you are your goddamn mind
Banner's not the problem she is
I thought I told you to stay home and watch MJ
yeah you did
and then she tells me I gotta come watch you
wait did she actually say that to you
are you blushing Daphne Dale
not blushing
God damn it I knew I should have brought a bigger gun
that's a good idea bring a bigger gun
what are you gonna do tickle him to death
no look
change your plan first we get this on the Hulk
then we go after Jean I got one better
that's the highest casualty producing threat
you contain it I go find the source
I take it down you got it
are you just trying to get out of fighting the Hulk
I guess so OK
whatever dude
I got this
oh you freak
freak freak what
do not kill her don't start with that soft serve bullshit
you know something I'm gonna do this
I'm gonna do it my way just just go
just go don't get within 33 feet yeah so frustrating
hey hey
whoa this guy's got issues
oh no
no not again
talk to banner
is that you Spider Man
what happened where am I
hey hey hey
did I do all this yeah
did I hurt anyone it's not your fault
she was in your mind you weren't in control
I lost my inhibitor look here here
it's the only thing keeping the monster inside
it's okay I got another one
I just need you to put this on
what is it it's universal it should work on you
please sir
there's people in the building just put it on
oh you okay
my head I think she broke something
is she still in there no
it's the other guy Bruce
oh look
I can get you out of here okay
I just need you to put that inhibitor on get away from me
it's coming
I can't get through
yes you can Bruce
yes you can get out of the building
get out of the building get out of the building
no no
banner please look at me
no banner no girl
oh me oh
I didn't know you could get that big
whoa
good luck with that Peter
there you are
just hold still just hold still
oh God
no lethal rounds
ah ah
tracking time to detonation
90 seconds to detonation I know I know
come on come on
why is your skin so thick
inhibitor cannot attack come on
Dr Bennet
please
Bruce
it's Peter
I'm your friend
throw down your guns or you get the next one in the head
where is she
what did you it's over Jean
Sarah
is that my gun
is anyone hurt
it's just me
Spider Man
you saved my life
and you saved God knows how many lives
by making sure she didn't find what she was looking for in there
before she passed out she tried to say something
a name Sarah
does that mean something to you before you got the inhibitor on her
she managed to get in my mind for a moment
Sarah was the name of someone I worked closely with
that recently passed I'm sorry to hear that
somehow the memory of Sarah must have affected her
well I'd love to talk to her when she wakes up
that's all right of course
she'll be transferred to our facility on Roosevelt Island
I'm just as eager to get her talking as you are
but let's not strain her too much in one day
yeah of course
thank you Spider Man my pleasure
Andrei it worked
she's in custody you're safe now
you left this
did you want me to find it
no no
um
look I can explain
can you take that off please
what
the mask
I think I deserve to have this conversation with Peter Parker
you came to the party at our apartment the other night
in the donut shop
the year I went off to school
why didn't you tell me then
I was trying to protect you yeah
well I've almost been killed like five times the past 24 hours
so it's not really working that well
I know I'm sorry I
were you ever gonna tell me
right
so you just were gonna make that decision for me
I know I'm sorry
I don't really need you to keep saying that you're sorry
I don't know what you want me to tell you
I want you to tell me why you would do this to me
I lost someone
and they'd still be here if it wasn't for me
I didn't read you that letter
because I didn't want anything like that to happen to you
but that's not really your decision
I know it's not but
you mean everything to me
and I've been trying to live my life without you but I
I can't
I love you
the spell or whatever it is that you did
user
all these memories that you're saying that we have together
I I don't
I don't have them
and I do see why you know she would love you
the girl you wrote that letter to but
I understand that you did what you had to do to protect her
and for that I'm so grateful
but I
I dont love you
he said I don't I don't even know you
I should probably go now
really I'm sorry Peter
I don't have a phone
um
do you mind taking me home
yeah of course thank you
huh huh
thank you yeah sure
um
I'm gonna uh uh yeah yeah of course
do you wanna come up
just to say hi to Ned maybe
I would love that
the Hulk aka Doctor Bruce Banner is in custody
currently being transferred to a psychiatric ward
so sad after years as a peaceful academic
the question the world asks today is what finally snapped
hey I'm nearby
hey I'm nearby MJ yeah hey
I'm nearby
huh hey
I'm your boy you're not gonna believe this hey
I'm your boy but the Spidey Tracker app
says that Spider Man is in the direct vicinity
oh yeah no way
that's crazy
hey I'm your boy
uh Ned
Spider Man Spider Man Ned
it's nice to meet you Ned hello
I'm I'm not like a weirdo or anything
he's a little weird why uh why
why are you here haha
oh I uh
I was I was on the subway platform right
and she was on her phone yeah
I got a little distracted and the train was coming
and I just swooped her right up saved me
oh my God
why is that never happened to me
so what if you're mid swing and you decide you need to pee
do you just land on top of a building
what do you drop down to ground level and run into a coffee shop
and you're like hey
it's Spider Man I need to pee or do you find a rooftop somewhere
no I don't find a rooftop somewhere Ned
is this really what you wanna be asking him right now
yeah dude come on you can ask me anything
you wanna know how my web shooters work
I mean I already know how the web shooters work is that right
well there's obviously some sort of sheer
thinning fluid that is cycling within a chamber right
so it can keep its liquid form
and then when you activate it by pressing all the triggers
it runs through a Teflon turbine
and then it hardens when it interacts with the air right
I I mean not exactly but okay okay
well then tell me what's in the web fluid
I guess something like a long chain polymer uh nylon
that's pretty close okay okay
what about Nomex or or Kevlar
all right then keep your secrets
if you're referring to the incident with the dragon
I was barely involved
all I did was simply give your uncle a little nudge
out the door hahaha
solid reference oh ban me time you ordered ban me's
I ordered 5 ban me's we have Spider Man in the apartment
he's gonna get fed hahaha
sorry about him
he's just like very excited that you're here are you kidding
this like the most fun I've had in years I really miss you guys
you guys really do look like best friends what do you mean
you should tell him he can handle it
yeah I know
um
when she was inhabiting you on the rooftop
she kissed me and I kissed her back because I I thought it was you
but I didn't know and I'm I'm really sorry
I just thought you should know
thanks for telling me
I mean it's not like I remember anything anyway so really yeah
it was weird it was like one second I was sitting at my desk
and the next second I was lying on the street
I don't know like a light switch went off
what so you don't remember anything
no why
that's good said he remembered thinking about someone named Sarah
but what you're saying is that you don't remember anything at all
I I mean yeah it was instantaneous that's what made it so scary
he lied to me
I heard you caught Leshy yeah
her name's Jean Grey
I need some help determining the size of some potatoes potatoes
I think that's Black Widow
I think Medzkar lied to me about her name
can you see if there's a connection between Jean and someone named
Sarah hmm
these potatoes sound meager
oh wow that really is your office well
well well internet
government records
and a lot of data related to Jean Grey has been scrubbed by
damage control data about what
her sister wait Jean has a sister
hmm
Sarah Gray also a telepath
damage control took her into custody for study and the observation wow
I mean you can probably guess what they mean by that
experimentation and other human rights violations yes
exactly wait
who are you hi
that leads big fan hi
I'm sorry I'm just so happy that the sad man has friends
uh ha ha thanks I I owe you one good luck Spider Man why
she was just looking for her sister
and I handed her to the people that took her
I gotta go OK Peter yeah
just be careful alright
yeah I will yeah
Spider Man's name is Peter
Jean
who do you wanna be
her pink jacket
she's too far you're gonna have to hop hop first
pick someone close and then
each hop has a limit
but you can string them together and go as far as you want
and when you let go
you're right back where you started
could you do that to everyone in this park at once
well yeah
maybe one day if you get really good
how could she just send us away
she wasn't really a mom
not like that anyway she was before we changed yeah
well if that's all it takes for you to stop being a mom
then you're not a mom
what would you do if you had daughters like us I'd love them
especially the redhead one shut up
we have each other
yeah we have ice cream
one mint chip one chocolate yeah
OK
now I know how you play
Sarah
I'm sorry Jean
I have to keep you safe
subject is awake heart rate is 94 bpm
Jean that's not gonna work anymore thanks to Spider Man
Jeanne
I need you to breathe I need you to look at me and breathe OK
you're safe breathe
where is she
like your sister you've been blessed with a power
that has the potential to do tremendous good in the world
or tremendous damage
a power like yours in the hands of a child is an impossible burden
but imagine
if that power was placed in the hands of people
who actually know what to do with it
where is my sister
you're gonna change the world Jean hey
hey
Frank I know where you are
what you're doing oh yeah
and how's that got eyes everywhere kid look Frank
damage control kidnapped Jean's sister
Jean was just trying to find her
we were wrong about everything
sentimental horseshit
you seen what she can do what she's capable of
what you gonna let her loose
is that what you're gonna do
tell you right now you do that I handle it my way Frank
please can you Frank
distance check 40 foot clearance locking down the room locking down
disengage inhibitor
Jean your powers are now fully operational
as you can tell we are beyond your jump radius tell me what VMAX is
you're the second person to ask me about that
I I have no idea what that means
she sent me a message she was trying to help me find her
she communicated with you telepathically across all that distance
we did register a huge spike in that session
fascinated what does it mean asshole
I don't know let's begin
our work with Sarah centered on two areas
identifying the source of her power
and identifying a path towards copying it
if we could find a way to record a telepathic brain during a jump
then perhaps
we could replicate those pathways in the mind of our choosing
this instrument is your sister's legacy
we built this together over many months of trial and error
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice
what are you talking about
trigger the first jump
tell me what VMAX is I know that's where you're hiding her
she's jumping
copy we're in full lockdown process has commenced what process
hey whoa
that's a pretty serious look there dude hey
hey whoa what the hell man
come on I'm a friend of damage control what are you doing
it's gonna be like that you wanna go alright
alright just give me a sec
give me a sec
I'm not in high school anymore oh
did you stretch you big stretcher
I mean you should do in your line of work
what about you you guys stretch
it's so good for you oh
you ready
wait
watch your head
ah ah
where is Jean Grey
let's jump 26 recordings look good
excuse me sir
we have an intruder
you were right she's much stronger than her sister
increase the frequency
you're doing very well Jean
Jean can you hear me
you're a murderer
her frequencies are evolving
this doesn't make sense the last thing my sister saw was this room
her brain waves are somehow affecting the objects around her
shut it down I'm trying sir
what do you mean you're trying
the last thing my sister saw was this goddamn room
shut it down I can't sir
move
I can't let you do that Bill
the only hands that will wield this power are mine
Bos never used 51bce0c785ca2f6808
what you want
Jean
I'm here to help you
you put me here I know
and I'm sorry about Sarah
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong
if you came here to save a helpless girl from damage control
you're too late
they're the ones who need saving
and now so do you
here we go
God that's cool
come on come on
what the
isn't it funny
how your friends from Damage Control developed a special weapon
just for you
they've got a whole task force ready
just in case you ever get out of line
people are monsters
you shouldn't trust them any more than they trust you
I'm a little busy Frank
you got a problem kid
you gotta hold everyone within a kilometer of the island
wait what
look if you're gonna do something
you better do it now I'm trying
good shit I'm the devil
my sister died in this room
surrounded by these men
and her only crime was that she was special
just like you
just like me
people like us don't get to live a normal life
we don't get to have friends or family
those people are gone
that life is over
so why don't you just be honest with yourself
are you Peter Parker
are you Spider Man
I'm both
Jean please
this won't make it right
come on you're not a killer Jean
you have no idea what I am
I know that you loved your sister
and I know that losing her felt like you'd lost everything
if you come any closer he dies they all do
you know this won't bring her back
right Jean you
don't be so sure I can't get into your mind
I'm a lot more powerful since I last tried
go ahead
hey
you think you don't have to listen to me now I've got powers
you know this
this whole thing can get really scary you know that
it's already pretty scary
yeah and things can change very quickly
in ways that we can't even imagine right now
I know
oh uh
I don't think you do know
what do you mean
you're a really special person
and I would hope that
that will always make you feel really great about yourself
but I know sometimes it doesn't
sometimes it'll be really lonely
and sometimes
because you're special
people can do dark
monstrous things to you
but
this is what I want you to know
you're beautiful
and the people who love you
we love you not because you're special
we love you because you're you
I want you to remember that
even when it feels like you're totally alone
that's your deepest responsibility
never forget that no matter how powerful you become
hey
I'm sorry about your sister
I'm sorry about your aunt
yeah you would have loved her
just because we've lost someone
it doesn't mean we have to do this alone
I mean
we can't trust me I've been trying
it doesn't work
even if that's true
I have no one
you have me
you hurt
no no fine
I'm okay
Peter I'm okay
I'm okay I'm okay Peter
Peter Peter no no
no no
no Peter
you gotta get out of here
they'll be looking for you no
no no
no please just stay with me
come on hold on
come on please
you're gonna be OK
just go
look at me
shock today
a Spider Man arrived at Bellevue Hospital with a bullet wound
seemingly at death's door
the reclusive crime fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical experts work to save him
tonight all eyes are on Spider Man
the hero who saved New York so many times
is now in the hands of its best and brightest
and the people of New York hold their breath
Frank
where am I
no no
no hey
where's my mask don't worry about that
I got you covered hey
you good where's Jean
is she okay yeah
she's okay she's okay where is she
I think maybe she just left
she was uh
using her magic voodoo shit to keep you alive
yeah she's alright
I'm sorry
Frank I'm just
just I'm I'm Frank
I'm really sorry for what I did
no Frank
and you know it's a lot of things
but it sure shit ain't OK alright
I seen
I seen real bravery kid my day
but that that
that was someone else
you crying
no I ain't
you know you look the exact way I thought you would
a nice kid
never had a friend like that
are we friends now
I can't believe I just saw you cry
ha ha ha cry
what are you talking about bullshit
oh yeah
they've been doing it all night
been here since you walked in just take a look
yo kid we came in
they had to cut through the suit
but when you're ready to split
I got a plan
hey it's Spider Man
Spider Man
you're the best Spider Man
over here
we love you you're the best Spider Man
it's Spider Man
Spider Man Spider Man
Spider Man Spider Man Spider Man
I've uh
been thinking a lot about what you said
and you'd be happy to know that I've decided I'm not
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore
I miss you mate
I mean I still got a little pain in my back
but I could probably get back out there
if you need me for anything
what I need you to do is rest
I know I know
but come on you gotta give me something
I mean how's the investigation going well
Metzger's still missing but your friend Black Widow
she's been helping us dig through all the records
Damage Control tried to have scrubbed
had me drop by her office the other day
and how was that well
uh my skin feels amazing
attention all units we have a confirmed bank robbery in progress
hey are you getting this
yeah I'm on it
hey it's not that far from me
I could probably meet you down there
no we can handle a robbery
just try to take care of yourself
okay
you too
say hello to EJ and Marley for me
okay
Spider Man says hello
hi uh hey
oh oh uh
flower guy right from from the party
I'm Peter
OK hello
user
New Spider Man sighting location unknown
location unknown
location found